This is channel four meteorologist Johnny Nimbus!
这里是4频道的气象学家强尼云雨
Coming at you live from the sight of tomorrow's holiday spectacular.
为您发回关于明天节日节目的现场报道
And I'm here alongside Pete Rooney,
我旁边的是皮特鲁尼
the Chairman of the Stevens Point tree lighting committee.
史蒂芬 圣诞树彩灯委员会主席
Now, Pete, I see a tree, not a lot of lights.
现在 皮特 我看到了一棵树 却没看到彩灯啊
Don't leave us in the dark. [Laughs]
别把我们置身于黑暗之中
Classic Nimbus.
真经典 云雨
But seriously, what have you got planned?
但说正的 你们有什么计划
Are we on the air now, like, now now?
我们现在在直播吗 就 现在
Now?
现在
Hi.
嗨
Uh, yeah we're live to over 50,000 viewers.
额，是的，我们面向五万观众直播
Although I think that number drops every second
尽管我认为那个数字每秒都在减少
you stand there like a frozen snowman.
你站那跟个雪人似的
Excuse me, Johnny. Hi. I'm Maddie Rooney, co-chair.
打扰一下 强尼 嗨 我是麦蒂鲁尼 联合主席
And think I could shed some light on that.
我认为我可以透漏一点光（一些事情）
[Laughs]
Classic Maddie. [Sighs]
真经典 麦蒂
So we envision a tree completely lit by candles.
我们打算用蜡烛点亮圣诞树
And we call it "Christmas unplugged".
我们叫它“不插电圣诞节”
Hmm. "Christmas unplugged".
嗯 “不插电圣诞节”
Well, last year the Griswold family lit their tree with lasers
嗯，去年格斯沃德一家用激光点亮了圣诞树
and then they had a stealth bomber fly over and drop tinsel, but hey...
然后他们用一个神秘的轰炸机飞过并放下了最上面的那颗球，不过嘿
I guess not everybody has to try.
我想不是每个人都能做到
- So... - Uh, wait.
所以 额 等一下
You didn't let me finish.
你没让我讲完
We were going to do the thing that I just said, but then we changed our
我们本打算做我刚刚说的事 不过我们改变
minds and came up with something bigger and better and more awesome-er.
主意了 并且想出了更盛大更好更棒的主意
All right. That's what Stevens Point wants to hear.
好的 那就是史蒂芬 想听到的
Come on, give me the deets. What have you got planned?
拜托  给我些提示 你们有什么计划
Merry Christmas.
圣诞快乐